https://myprivacychoices.drhorton.com/?op=op1&src=D1H0

Processing...
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Request My Personal Information
Delete My Personal Information
We do not sell or rent customer lists to unaffiliated third parties for marketing or any other purposes. At times, we may share your personal
information with third parties as described in our Privacy Policy. If you are a resident of certain locations, such as California or the European
Economic Area, you may request that we refrain from selling or, in certain cases, sharing your personal information. To request that D.R. Horton
refrain from selling or sharing your personal information as described under applicable law, please provide the information below, and visit
our Cookie Consent Tool to control the sharing of information with third parties via cookies and similar technologies. If you have any
questions, you may contact us at 888-559-2763 or PrivacyManager@drhorton.com.
To submit a request to access your personal information, please fill out the form below. If you have any questions, you
may contact us at 888-559-2763.
To submit a request to delete your personal information, please fill out the form below. If you have any questions, you
may contact us at 888-559-2763.
Request Type:
Have you purchased a D.R. Horton home? *
Zip Code:
Select Address:
Have you leased a home from D.R. Horton? *
Zip Code:
Select Address:
Have you requested a quote or purchased insurance from D.R. Horton Insurance Agency? *
Please provide your policy number:*
Have you requested or obtained a mortgage or pre-qualification for a mortgage through DHI Mortgage for your home purchase / refinance? *
Please provide your loan number:*
Did you utilize DHI Title for your home purchase / refinance? *
Please provide your escrow number:*
Please tell us when and where you have communicated with us in the past (for example, visited a sales or leasing office).
If you have not previously purchased a home from us or communicated with us in the past, please tell us why you think D.R. Horton has your information.
autorenew
record_voice_over
check_circle
Captcha text is required
check
close
SUBMIT
